

JaeWon Lee

ROBOTICS · MULTI-ROBOT · SLAM

25, Galmaejungang-ro, Guri-si, Gyeonggi-do, 11902, Rep. of KOREA

□ (+82) 10-9114-2756 | 🗷 ashcircle@kw.ac.kr | 🔏 lee-jaewon.github.io | 🖸 Lee-JaeWon

"Passion is the genesis of genius."

Summary

This is Jaewon Lee, who wants to be a Multi-Robot engineer and Cooperative Autonomous Driving engineer. I am interested in Robotics, SLAM, Multi-Robot System. I think Robotics can help the development of the world a lot. I want to study a lot and approach the world.

Research Interests

Multi-Robot Exploration, Navigation, Path Planning, Collision Avoidance, Map Fusion

SLAM Visual SLAM, Visual Odometry, Optimization

Education

KwangWoon University

Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS

Mar. 2020 - Feb. 2024(Expected)

- Current GPA: 4.06/4.50, Current Major GPA: 4.28/4.50
- Club: BARAM Robotics (Robotics Academic Group) [2022 Vice President], Mar.2020-Present

Work Experience_

Robotics A.I. LAB. @KwangWoon Univ

Seoul, S.Kored

Undergraduate LAB Intern (Advisor: PROF. Junghyun Oh)

Jan. 2022 - Jun. 2022

- Research on Visual SLAM and Computer Vision
- Studying Visual SLAM and implementing Multi-Robot SLAM, Exploration and Path-Planning

ROBOMATION

R&D INTERN

Songpa-gu, Seoul, S.Korea

Jun. 2022 - Present

- Research and Development Intern
- Development of Automation System for Soccer Games Using Multi-Robots and GUI for Communication.

Honors & Awards _____

AWARDS

2022 **Dean's list**, for Academic Excellence (First Place in the Spring Semester)

Kwangwoon Univ.

Skills

Programming C++/C, Python, Matlab

DevOps ROS, Git

Framework Pytorch, Tensorflow, Keras, Unity

Languages Korean, English

Extracurricular Activity _____

Technical Blog - lee-jaewon.github.io

Personal Tech Blog Jul. 2021 - Present

WRITER

• Writing posts about paper review, development, study of Interests.

Studying through writing and sharing.

August 4, 2022 JaeWon Lee · curriculum vitae

Technical Team Blog - ropiens.tistory.com

Co-Writer

Jul. 2022 - Present

• Writing posts about paper review, development, study of Interests.

· Studying through writing and sharing.

2022 Open Source Contribution Academy

Ministry of Science and ICT, NIPA

MENTEE

Jul. 2022 - Present

· Contributions to translating Pytorch Hub English documents into Korean at the Pytorch Korean User's Group.

Autonomous Driving Simulation with Reinforcement Learning

BARAM Robotics

PERSONAL TOY PROJECT

Sep.2021 - Nov.2021

- · Autonomous-driving simulation through DQN Reinforcement algorithm in self-made simulator with unity.
- Reward management using DQN, CNN, and Laser Sensor.
- The source code for the project is in [my GitHub repository].

Frontier Based Multi-Robot Exploration

BARAM Robotics

PERSONAL TOY PROJECT

Mar.2022 - Jun.2022

- Implementation of ROS-based Multi-Robot SLAM.
- Implementing Frontier Based Exploration and Allocation Algorithm.
- The source code for the project is in [my GitHub repository].

House Interior Classifier and Automatic Recommendation

2022 Deep Learnina Lecture

Mar.2022 - Jun.2022

DEEP-LEARNING PROJECT

- Implementation House Interior Classifier.
- This can be automatically recommended on the actual sales site with classified result.
- Using Inception-Resnet-V2 in Keras
- The source code for the project is in [my GitHub repository].

Educational Activities

AI Genius Academy Mentoring

Organized by Micro School, TresC3

Nov.2021

TEACHING ASSISTANT

TEACHING ASSISTANT

- · Project Assistant with Arduino and Raspberry Pi
- Support students to experience AI and proceed with the project through a Teachable Machine.

Samsung Electronics App Development Mentoring

Organized by Micro School TresC

Ian 2022

• MIT App Inventor training and Project Assistant.

AUGUST 4, 2022

JAEWON LEE · CURRICULUM VITAE